原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译   千只鹤飞过波千鸟  tong大梨
翻译   AlgerDestiny  Stampy  五天
翻译   马丁马丁回音山  不见喜茶  VC
校对     屯栗子
时间轴     兜兜兜爹
后期     渔夫
总监     屯栗子
辛普森一家
第三十一季  第十九集
他们想让我回去吗
They want me back?
这熊孩子怎么让我干这个的
春田第一教堂
捐款募资
我们西女更夕字母
今天没人来
No one's here today.
就连合唱团都迟到了
Even the choir's late.
*迈克尔  走拼车道*
*Michael, take the carpool lane*
*哈利路亚*
*Hallelujah*
*他们刚刚跨越了双黄线*
*They just crossed the double line*
*教教他们交通规则*
*Traffic school them*
老妈  这么多空位
Mom, with all the room,
我们非得跟怪老头坐这么近吗
do we have to sit so close to the geezers?
-太热了  -太冷了
- It's too hot. - It's too cold.
我其实都死了
I'm not even alive.
琼·里弗斯什么时候来
What time does Joan Rivers come on?
她不来了
She doesn't.
这是教堂  不是你家
This is a church, and it's not your church.
新版圣经
New Testament?
我的老天爷这啥时候的事儿
Oy-yoi-yoi, when did this happen?
Alexa  播放宁静管风琴音乐
Alexa, play Tranquil Organ Radio.
平安与你们同在
Peace be with you.
也与你同在
And also with you.
你们可以喊得更响亮
Oh, you can do better than that.
我们可以  但我们不想
We can, but we don't want to.
我听不见
I can't hear you.
你明显听得见
You clearly can.
主啊  要么让这个变得有趣
Lord, either make this interesting
要么给我点狂喜的活动吧
or just rapture me now.
好货送
三天祈祷加禁食
到期的
使劲榨干他们吧  弟兄们
Salt the ham water, boys.
克兰西·韦根就要达标了
Clancy Wiggum is meeting his quota.
那是违法的
Hey! That's illegal.
抱歉  这样吧
Oh, sorry. You know what?
拿着  给你二十五美分吧警长
Here. Have a quarter, Chief.
你觉得你可以用这么点钱贿赂我  我的妈呀
You think you can bribe me with a...? Oh, my God!
这是一双我见过最温柔的眼睛
Those are the gentlest eyes I've ever seen.
亚麻衬衫  自然的光辉
Linen shirt. Natural highlights.
你要拿我的枪吗
You want to hold my gun?
你可以拿
Y-You can.
多谢  我正希望你可以告诉我
Thanks. I was hoping maybe you could point me
镇上的教堂怎么走
to the church in town.
教堂  这条街直走  第一个看见的尖顶
Church? Yeah, straight down this street. First steeple you see.
不是教堂  那是埃菲尔铁塔脱衣舞吧
That is not it. That's the Eiffel Tower strip club.
他们的法式洋葱汤真的
They have a French onion soup that is,
也就还行吧
uh, well, it's just okay.
我想
And I guess
我就说这么多
that's about all.
你将不再让我感到无聊
You shall bore me no more!
你走反了
You're going the wrong way!
不  我正要走这边  我爱上帝
No, I-I want to go this way. I love God.
你这么爱他  不如嫁给他
If you love him so much, why don't you marry him?
零钱  纽扣
Penny. Button.
我欠你一分钱
IOU for one penny.
你好  我是伯德·莱特
Hi. Bode Wright.
康复会在楼下
Recovery meetings are downstairs.
戒酒的去右边  戒药的去左边
Booze to the right, huffers to the left.
抱歉  我看了广告来的  基督徒专用清单网
Sorry, I'm here about the ad. On Christslist?
你们需要一个年轻牧师对吗
About you guys needing a-a youth pastor?
我没放什么广告
I didn't place any ad.
是我放的
I placed the ad.
基督徒求贤清单
-我是伯德  -伯德  十字架很好看
- I'm Bode. - Bode. Nice cross.
提姆的被嚼成小疙瘩了
Tim's are chewed to nubs.
我会嚼十字架  紧张时候的习惯
I-I chew my crosses. Nervous habit.
你有经验吗  伯德
Do you have any experience, Bode?
我在密歇根工作过
I used to work in Michigan.
不得不使用瓶装的圣水
Had to use bottled holy water.
教育背景呢
Education?
我有神学硕士学位
I, uh, have a master's in divinity
研究方向是圣经语言
with a focus on biblical languages.
-希腊语  希伯来语  -你被雇佣了
- Greek, Hebrew... - You're hired.
不不不不不  不能这么快
Up-bup-bup-bup-bup! It doesn't work that fast.
要填就业资格验证表  工资税收报表  试领结
We have I-9s and W-2s, collar fittings.
而且话说回来  这里我说了算
And, besides, I'm the one in charge.
说到底  这里不是主说了算吗
In the end, isn't God in charge here?
你见过吉米·巴菲特本人光临自己的咖啡馆吗
Do you see Jimmy Buffett at every Jimmy Buffett café?
我觉得不会
I don't think so.
这个能送我吗
Hey, can I have this?
我上厕所的时候马姬可以用这个喂我零食
Marge could use it to serve me snacks while I'm on the toilet.
拿去吧
Oh, just take it.
伯德  你现在有落脚的地方吗
So, Bode, do you have anywhere to stay?
还没有  我在废轮胎厂旁看到一家汽车旅馆
Not yet. I saw a motel by the tire fire.
汽车旅馆
盛大开幕
-他和我们一起住  -没门
- He'll stay with us. - No way.
神父  流浪汉们来洗脚了
Uh, Reverend? The homeless are here for their foot washing.
我希望能修剪指甲做蜜蜡修眉
I'm looking for a mani-pedi and an eyebrow wax.
我猜我这里需要一些帮助
I guess I could use a little help around here.
谢谢  我不会让你失望的
Thank you. I won't let you down.
我们这不来拥抱这套
We don't hug here.
我是来参加匿名戒酒会的
Uh, I'm here for the Alcoholics Anonymous meeting.
通常有我  莱尼  卡尔  黄蜂人和肯特·布罗克曼
It's usually me, Lenny, Carl, Bumblebee Man, Kent Brockman.
但是别告诉别人
But don't tell anyone.
楼下右转
Downstairs to the right.
还有  大厨朵拉  图特国王
Also, Lunchlady Dora, King Toot,
还有个人  我叫他迪斯科S
and a man I'll identify as Disco S.
迪斯科S就是个烂摊子
Disco S is quite a mess.
春田镇第一教堂
今日问题婚姻
辛普森夫妇
马姬  这也太尴尬了
Oh, Marge, this is embarrassing.
我们不需要做咨询
We don't need counseling.
我们需要做咨询
We do need counseling.
我现在一肚子火
I'm carrying a lot of anger.
那就像我一样  回家去
Just do what I do. Come home
有一顿热乎的晚餐在等待着你
and have a hot dinner waiting for you.
我要说我没有任何先入为主的想法
Well, let me just say that I go into this with no preconceptions.
跟我说说  侯默错在哪了
Now, tell me, how is this Homer's fault?
他没告诉我就把我家房子卖了
He sold our home without telling me.
海伦  他在玩我的火车吗
Helen, is he playing with my damn trains?
抱歉  楼下勒弗乔伊岔口出了问题
Excuse me. There's trouble down at Lovejoy Junction.
那我们没事了吧
So, we're good?
我们能拿回房子那才没事了
We're good if we get our house back.
你说的是船上房子吗
Did you say houseboat?
拿回房子  拿回房子
House back. House back!
春田镇第一教堂
如果你是主
那你到家了
抱歉神父  我是想休息一会
Sorry, Reverend. I'm trying to get some rest?
去特伦顿的12号线
The 12 to down Trenton doesn't stop
不能因为你的大脑袋就停下
just because your fat head's on the track.
春田镇铁路
-你在做什么  -没什么
- What are you doing? - Nothing.
-你要把这玩意扔下来吗  -不是
- You gonna drop that? - Not doing a thing.
你的恶作剧就是要把小木棍扔在我脸上
As a gag, you're gonna drop a tiny log on my face?
-不是  -在我睡着的时候这样做  太好笑了
- Nothing. - As I'm sleeping? That's, that's-that's funny.
- 不是  没有  -来吧  扔下来
- Nothing. Nothing. - Go ahead. Drop it.
-把木棍扔在我脸上  -没有
- Drop a tiny log on me. - Not doing a thing.
这就是你的计划  你要扔下来吗
Is that... Is that your plan? You're gonna drop that?
听着  我们都老大不小了
Look, we're both grown men here.
离我的小火车远点
Now leave my choo choo alone.
乐意之至
Gladly.
很高兴能用上这招
Glad I finally got to use that.
我睡眼惺忪的年轻伙伴
Now, my sleepy, young friend,
我不知道你在密歇根州是如何行事的
I don't know how you did things back in "Michigan."
手势引号意味着这不是真的
Air quotes are for when something's not a real thing.
但是在我的教区  我们为教众服务
But in my parish, we minister to our flock.
我敢说必要且难以启齿的事情
And I'm not afraid to say the hard things that need to be said.
I  二十七
"I" 27.
-什么  -他刚才说什么
- What? - What did he say?
我们听不到
We can't hear you.
B  三
"B" Thr-three.
我很乐意帮你把号码喊出来
You know, I'd be happy to yell out numbers for you.
让你少说话
Help save your voice.
宾戈游戏需要一位严肃且经验丰富的主持人
Bingo requires a firm, experienced caller.
G  G  四十八
"G" "G" 48.
N  四  N  四十三
"N" Four... "N" 43.
我啥也没有
I got nothing.
我想我能胜任
I think I can handle it.
我在神学院的时候
When I was in seminary school,
我是我们划船队里嗓门最大的人
I was the shouty guy on our rowing team.
我们当时不让说舵手这个词
We weren't allowed to say "Coxswain."
宾戈游戏不适合新手
Bingo is not for newbies.
字母的发音很容易混淆
The letters sound very similar.
B  十五
"B" 15.
基督教传统中朝拜初生耶稣的东方三圣贤之一
B就是巴尔萨泽
"B" as in Balthazar.
他刚才说的是加尔萨泽吗
Did he say Galthazar?
中了
Gingo!
金格带你去厕所
Gingo take you to bathroom.
我不想去
I don't want to go.
这对我来说也太难了
Hey, this no picnic for Gingo either.
又空荡荡的
Empty again.
那两人只是过来亲热的
And those two just came here to make out.
如果我们在教堂做的话  就不能怀孕了
If we do it in a church, I, like, can't get pregnant.
早上
Uh, good mor...
抱歉
Excuse me.
兄弟姐妹们
Brothers and sisters,
勒弗乔伊牧师的嗓音有些问题
Reverend Lovejoy is experiencing some vocal difficulties.
少说话  牧师
Save your voice, Reverend.
现在  我们取消教堂活动
Now, we could cancel church.
上帝已经预见到了这次意外
But God clearly foresaw this
还派来了替补牧师帮忙完成礼拜
and sent us a backup pastor to finish the service.
教堂活动不会取消了
Church will not be canceled.
现在有请我们新来的年轻牧师伯德·莱特
Now please help me welcome our new youth minister Bode Wright.
谢谢  很谦恭  耶稣会喜欢的
Thanks. That's very meek. Jesus would've loved it.
我在想  当牧师在休整的时候
I was thinking, while the reverend rests his voice,
也许我们可以合唱一首歌
maybe we could all sing a song.
牧师  如果你同意的话  咳嗽一声
Uh, Rev, if that's okay with you, um, cough once.
我们不懂两声咳嗽是什么意思
We did not establish what two coughs means,
我就当作是两声同意了
so I'll take that to mean two yeses.
我们唱首歌好不好
Why don't we sing, I don't know,
《奇异恩典》怎么样  你们都熟悉这首
"Amazing Grace"? You all know that one.
如果不熟  这首歌在你的赞美诗集中
Or if you don't, it's in your hymnal under
《奇异  逗号  恩典》那里
"Grace, comma, amazing."
*奇异恩典  何等甘甜*
*Amazing grace, how sweet the sound*
*我罪已得赦免*
*That saved a wretch like me*
*前我失丧  今被寻回*
*I once was lost but now I'm found*
*也曾失明  如今复明*
*'Twas blind, but now I see.*
这是在白人教堂里发生过的
This is the most exciting thing that ever happened
最激动人心的事了
in a white church!
这么多年的恩典都平平无奇
All these years of mediocre grace.
终于有奇异恩典了
Finally, it's amazing.
耶稣基督的音乐会肯定
This must've been what it was like
就是这样
at Jesus's concerts.
谢谢你们  现在我们
Thank you. Now we'd,
我们来唱几首新圣歌
we'd like to do a couple of new psalms.
-*哈利路亚  哈利路*  -*哈利路亚*
- *Hallelujah, hallelu* - *Hallelujah*
*哈利路亚  哈利路*
*Hallelujah, hallelu*
哈利路亚
*Hallelujah*
教堂里正有大事发生
Something exciting's happening at the church.
我们去看看
Let's check it out.
好了  我想我们都懂  恩典是奇异的
All right, I think we get it. Grace, it's amazing.
我知道大部分人都会在礼拜结束前
I know most of you usually save your "Hallelujahs"
才唱《哈利路亚》
for when church is over.
我喜欢这种随意范儿
I adore the informality.
但如果可以的话  我想我或许可以
But if it's okay, I thought maybe I could just speak
与你们开诚布公地谈一谈
to you guys straight from my heart.
我事先没有任何准备
I don't have anything planned,
但我想我该谈谈有关上帝的事  对吧
but I guess I should talk about God, right?
身处教堂  身为牧师
Church. Pastor.
我是该谈谈有关上帝的事
Makes sense I should talk about God.
其实  我今早醒来的时候
But the truth is, I woke up this morning
不是很确定我是否信仰上帝
and I wasn't really sure if I believed in God.
没有上帝
No God?
堵住耳朵  孩子们
Fingers in your ears, boys.
堵得死死的
Till you can feel the brain.
没关系  没事的
It's okay. Everything's fine.
我  我只是醒来感觉有些疑虑
I-I just woke up with some doubt.
和在座的大多数人一样  我确定
Like many of you did, too, I'm sure.
世上有太多的伤痛和苦难
There's so much pain and suffering in the world,
我不确定是否真的有人在那里
I wasn't sure anyone was really out there.
在云端看着我们
Watching us. On a cloud.
这是我们想象中的上帝  是吧
That's how we think of God, right?
对于大多数人  上帝只是个监控无死角的
To many of us, God is just an angry, old miser
易怒的老吝啬鬼
with a killer surveillance system.
大家都挑吝啬鬼的刺儿
Everyone picks on the miser.
麻利点刮  不然没小费
Shave faster or no tip!
我麻利点  好的
I shave-a faster, all right.
快点  我要去出席葬礼
Hurry up. I'm going to a funeral.
您要去出席葬礼  好的
You're going to a funeral, all right.
这可真是磨洋工
This is taking too long.
我不能再这么拖延了
I got to stop procrastinating.
然后我静下心来思考这件事
Then I got quiet and thought about it.
我突然醒悟  上帝可能不在云端
It hit me that maybe God isn't up there, you know.
所谓的在别处
"Somewhere else."
上帝可能此刻就在这里
Maybe God's right here and now.
触手可及
As close as the air on your skin.
我第一次不再感到孤单
For the first time ever, I don't feel alone.
活着真美好
Life is worth living.
我雇你杀我的交易取消
Hey, forget that hit I called on myself, huh?
已经太迟了
Yeah, well, I said too late.
你就不能只收我跟踪费吗
Can't you just charge me a stalking fee?
好吧  百分之四十
Okay, 40%.
而且你只能在应用软件上取消
And you can only cancel on the app.
好吧  那我
All right, I-I'll just, uh...
我手机卡死了
My screen is frozen!
已删除  消息读取失败
无法取消
或许上帝只是我们共同创造和铭记的
Maybe God is just a word for a love
爱的代名词
that we create and remember together.
这种爱不会因被质疑而气愤
A love that isn't mad at us for our doubt
不会因你是酒鬼而发怒
or angry at us because we're alcoholics.
终于  我的成就得到了认可
Finally, recognized for my accomplishments.
我们多数人心中的上帝都以自己为原型
I think so many of us have made a God that's like us,
而不是别的参照物
instead of the other way around.
上帝爱多样性
God loves diversity.
他不止创造了一种花
God didn't just make one type of flower.
世间存在着数以千计的品种
He made thousands of different flowers--
玫瑰  百合  兰花
roses, lilies, orchids--
野草也同时生出
and He made the weeds, too.
但他一视同仁
But He loves all of them indiscriminately.
像蜜蜂那样
Just like the bees.
你令本骄傲黄蜂人感到羞愧
You have made this bumblebee a humble bee.
耶稣曾说  "让野草和麦子一同生长"
Jesus said, "Let the weeds grow with the wheat."
这意味着它们都得到了上帝的庇护
That means it's all in the game.
跟自己和解吧
Go easy on yourself.
你无需去赢得上帝的爱
You don't have to earn God's love.
你就是上帝的爱
You are God's love.
好  就到这吧
All right, that's it.
虽然很早  但天气这么好
I know it's early, but it's a beautiful day.
咱们出去吧
Let's get out of here.
耶稣巡演
抱歉哥们  演唱会结束了
Sorry, concert's over, dude.
就剩周边了
All that's left is the merch.
伯德  伯德  伯德
Bode! Bode! Bode!
为勒弗乔伊神父欢呼三声
Three cheers for Reverend Lovejoy.
蠢弗兰德斯
Stupid Flanders.
蠢弗兰德斯  蠢弗兰德斯
Stupid Flanders! Stupid Flanders!
我爱做礼拜
I love church.
那我在天堂不会孤单了
I won't be single in Heaven.
这是我做过的最好的礼拜
This was the best church ever.
就像某种宗教新体验似的
It was like some kind of religious experience.
愿意跟我们一起去吃煎饼吗
Will you join us for pancakes?
这是新祭服吗
Are those new vestments?
虔诚得熠熠生辉
They really bring out the piety.
你不必同情地奉承我  内德
You don't have to patronize me, Ned.
你说得对  对不起
You're, y-you're right, I'm sorry.
你今天表现挺糟糕的
Y-You did not do well today.
还是同情吧
Oh, go back to patronizing.
要不说说我的鞋
Maybe something about my shoes?
看看这鞋  系得这么紧  成圈也均匀
Oh, look at those shoes, tied so tight with loops so even.
看来某人掌握了兔子耳系带技巧
Someone knows the bunny ear technique.
海伦系的
Helen tied them.
更美好餐厅
煎饼  华夫饼  棒球收藏品
牧师  你愿意做祷告吗
Uh, Pastor, would you like to say grace?
主啊
Lord--
抱歉  我没说准确
Oh, sorry, I should have been more specific.
我是指大家都喜欢的新来的酷牧师
I meant the cool new pastor everyone likes.
你坐吧
You can sit down.
我觉得不需要我说
You know, I think the food is good
这饭菜本身就是美味的
without me saying it's good.
上帝让它美味可口
God made it good.
别误会  有感激之心是好事
Don't get me wrong, it's nice to be thankful, but
但是也没必要对着饭菜祈祷
there's no need to make everyone uncomfortable
搞得所有人都不舒服  对吧
by praying in front of 'em, am I right?
说得不错  就是比饭前祷告还长
Nice speech, although longer than grace.
我不吃培根
Oh, no bacon for me.
我是素食主义者
I'm a vegetarian.
其实我信佛
And, actually, a Buddhist.
挺好  我喜欢佛教
Great. I love Buddha.
我就是因此得名
That's where I got my name.
菩提树
The Bodhi Tree.
我也不吃肉
And I don't eat meat either.
你也是素食主义者吗
You're a vegetarian?
-那进化呢  -我信
- What about evolution? - Into it.
-同性恋权益呢  -大爱无边
- Gay rights? - Love is love.
迪兹还是大鸟
Dizzy or Bird?
大鸟及查理·帕克  二人曾合作录音
约翰·柯川和艾灵顿公爵  1962年
John Coltrane and Duke Ellington, 1962.
柯川与公爵在1962年合作了爵士专辑
要形容你刚对于爵士问题的回答有多完美
The only way to describe how perfect
最好的方式就是用爵士乐
that jazz answer is, is with jazz.
这顿早午饭已经变成了
This brunch has turned into...
爵士早午饭
a jazz brunch!
我是个信徒
I'm a believer.
挺好的  丽莎  但我真的觉得
That's great, Lisa, but I actually don't think
信仰不会归结为我们相信的东西
faith comes down to what we believe.
你总得相信这些鬼话
Well, you got to believe in this baloney.
你就是这么上天堂的
That's how you get into Heaven.
或许  就是或许  我在天堂
Where maybe, just maybe, I could see
还能再见到遗弃我的妈妈
the mother that abandoned me again.
把篮子还给我
是没错  但是我觉得只要合作
Yeah, sure, but I think together
我们就能在生时  把人间变成天堂
we can bring Heaven here while we're still alive.
有句中国谚语是说天堂与地狱的
There's a Chinese proverb about Heaven and Hell.
他们说地狱有张这样长的桌子  满是美食
They say Hell is a long table like this, full of food,
但是每个人都挨着饿  因为筷子很长
but everybody's starving because they have these long chopsticks,
就像台球杆  所以他们没法把食物吃进嘴
like pool cues, and they can't bring the food to their mouths.
这是最难受的牛年了
This is the worst Year of the Ox ever.
但是谚语中  天堂也是同样的桌子和食物
But in the proverb, Heaven is the exact same table, same food,
同样长的筷子  但是所有人幸福温饱
same long chopsticks, but everybody's happy and fat
因为他们互相喂吃的
because they're feeding each other.
等等  我也懂幽默
Wait, wait! I can be cool, too... with humor.
你们听没听过希腊人和犹太人结婚的笑话
Did you hear the one about the Greek-Jewish wedding?
他们不知道该摔盘子还是摔杯子
They didn't know whether to break the plates or the glasses!
按照习俗  希腊人摔盘子  犹太人摔杯子
你怎么不带着你的文化漠视
Yes, why don't you take your cultural insensitivity
回你该回的西班牙异端裁判所去
back to the Spanish Inquisition you came from?
15世纪设立于西班牙的罗马天主教会组织  因残酷迫害异教而知名
我失去他们了
I've lost them.
你从来就不拥有我们
You never had us.
勒弗乔伊神父
提默西  教会想感谢你
Timothy, the church council wants to thank you
多年来的
for your many years of...
无能
Incompetence!
把他的神父服扒了
Knock his frock off.
我们喜欢穿着紧身牛仔裤的新人
We like the new guy in his tight jeans.
别想着事业复苏
Do not resuscitate your career.
你们在说什么  要解雇我吗
What are you saying? You're firing me?
-金格  -请上交你的十字架
- Gingo. - Please surrender your cross.
我们不想惹麻烦
We don't want any trouble.
提默西
Timothy.
现在调领子
Now the collar.
停止服务
任何你转化过的圣水
And any water you turned into holy water
现在都变成普通的水了
is once again regular water.
都是自来水
Nothing but tap.
你知道伯德在油管上有两万二千个粉丝吗
Did you know Bode has 22,000 YouTube subscribers?
我们的教堂要火了
Our church could go viral.
关闭窗口
Ugh. Close window.
-你刚刚订阅了  -什么  不要
- You just subscribed. - What? No.
你刚给他点了个赞
Now you gave him a thumbs-up.
别唠叨了
Stop telling me what I just did.
你刚给他发送了一个茄子表情
You just gave him an eggplant emoji.
至少这表情不会造成误解
Well, at least that can't be misconstrued.
等等
Wait a minute.
我可以利用网络  找点他的黑历史
The Internet can help me. Help me find something on him.
谷歌上什么都搜不到
He's clean on Google.
我去必应搜搜看
I'll have to try Bing.
不好意思  刚刚睡着了
Sorry, I was asleep.
你确定要用我们搜索吗
Do you really want to use us?
是的
Yes.
啥也没有
Hmm. Nothing.
但我不认输
But I'm not licked.
准备好行李  海伦
Pack your bags, Helen.
我们出发去密歇根
We are going to Michigan.
牧师  我们来做咨询
Reverend? We're here for a little counseling?
乐意效劳
Well, I'd be happy to.
但你们身边已经有最棒的顾问了
But you're already with the best counselor there is.
你们彼此
Your partner.
等等  马姬总是和我说
Wait. But Marge always told me
交流对婚姻是有害的
communication is bad for a marriage.
我是说有益
I said it was good.
你说什么有益
You said what was good?
你们只是需要
You just have to know what it's like
站在对方的角度考虑[穿对方的鞋]
to be in each other's shoes.
我说真的  把鞋子换一下
Literally. Put on each other's shoes.
现在
Right now.
那好吧
All right then.
你的鞋太紧了
Your shoes are so tight.
还要每天穿着做家务
And you do so much work.
你真是个天使
You're an angel.
你的鞋太重了
And your shoes are so heavy.
我从来不知道你有这么重的负担
I never realized you carried around so much.
我仿佛又见到了令我倾心的那个男人
I'm starting to see the man I fell in love with again.
在哪呢  在哪  我杀了他
Where? Where? I'll kill him!
是你
You.
不得不说  这感觉真好
I must admit, this is amazing.
但他把我们的房子卖了这事怎么处理
But what about the fact that he sold our house?
-我能插句话吗  -当然
- Um, may I interject? - Sure.
我见过你们的房子  肯定没法通过检查
I've seen your house. It'll never pass inspection.
-你确定吗  -惨不忍睹
- Are you sure? - Piece of crap.
谢谢你  牧师
Thank you, Reverend.
《时间简史》
丽莎  什么风把你吹来了
Lisa. What brings you here?
我们来一起冥想吧  一定很有趣
Well, I thought it might be fun if we meditate together.
当然可以  自在点[home的h和e不发音即om]
Sure. Make yourself at om.
我听过这么多冥想的笑话里...
Wow! As meditation jokes go...
其实我只听过你这一个冥想笑话
That's the only meditation joke I've ever heard.
Alexa  播放冥想歌单
Alexa, play Meditation Jam.
知道吗  科学上称之为"意识"
You know, science calls it consciousness,
神秘学上称之为"灵魂"  但终究只是代称
the mystics call it a soul, but both are just words,
只是标签罢了  不论如何称呼它
just labels, for whatever it is
此时此刻正直视着你的双眼
that's looking out your eyes right now.
深呼吸  丽莎
Breathe, Lisa.
动画制作经费超额
你想见到上帝吗
是/否
你看见按钮了吧
Saw the button, huh?
没错
I did.
即将进入密歇根州
真的吗  你确定吗
米其林指南
密歇根州
提姆  我们可以去麦基诺岛
Tim, we could go to Mackinac Island.
那里有世界上最长的酒店门廊
They have the longest hotel porch in the world.
你到哪都是为了大阳台  不是吗  海伦
It's always the big verandas with you, isn't it, Helen?
你为这小镇做了一些
You've done something to this town
我觉得不可能会发生的事情
I never thought could happen.
一次全方位的宗教复兴
A full-blown religious revival.
好了  就让这些从内而外温暖你们
Yeah, let these warm your insides
就像圣保罗温暖你们的灵魂一样
as the words of St. Paul warm your soul, there.
亲爱的《以弗所书》
Dear Ephesians--
出自《新约圣经》  由使徒保罗所作
当然了  以下是我改写的
and I'm, of course, paraphrasing here--
信奉基督  否则我就用球棒敲你的头
believe in Christ or I'll hit your head with a baseball bat.
我肯定会照做的
I'll frickin' do it.
阿门
Amen.
我不是想改变人们的想法
Hey, I'm-I'm not trying to change any minds.
我只是想试着开始跟人交谈
I'm just trying to start a conversation.
我们需要这个  这小镇就像个雪花玻璃球
We need that. This town's like a snow globe.
看起来压根不像  除非你摇晃一下
It doesn't look like much till you shake it up a little.
我想要救赎  否则  老兄
I want redemption or else, dude.
否则什么
Or else what?
否则曼凯维奇拉比[犹太教教士]就会替代你  老兄
Or Rabbi Mankiewicz will, dude.
我不太会发那个"光"音
And I have trouble making that "Cch" Sound.
要么是"哐明节"  要么就是"咣明节"
It's either Chanukah or Hanukkah.
好吗  选一个吧
Okay? Pick one of those.
遍历城市新闻
一切新闻都在两页之间
帅气牧师在复活节被罢免
教会一个人用微缩胶片
Teach a man to microfiche,
你就会让他一辈子背负耻辱
and you'll feed him dirt for a lifetime.
大仇将报  吾如是说
Vengeance is mine, sayeth the me.
我们真该把那东西数字化的
We really should've digitized that stuff.
未完待续
但愿第二部是关于营救我的
Oh, I hope part two is about my rescue.
不  并不是
下周的  "向神父宣战第二部"
Next week on "Warrin' Priests Part Two..."
我听说之前那位
I hear there's a little dirt
在这里布道的人身上有些污点
on the collar of a man who used to preach here,
伯德·莱特
Bode Wright.
帅气牧师在复活节被罢免
你  先生  因为《圣经》质疑了我
You, sir, have challenged me on scripture.
如果你想说《圣经》的话
Oh, well, if it's scripture you want to talk,
那我们就“全地都要向耶和华欢乐”
then let us make a joyful noise unto the Lord.
引用自《旧约圣经》中的《诗篇》98:4
很好
Good.
如果激进主义不查收要它还有何用
Yarr, activism means nothing if it's not intersectional. Yarr!
敬请期待下周的《辛普森一家》
Next week on The Simpsons.